This is what war feels like
Korengal is a documentary, war film directed by Sebastian Junger.
Korengal picks up where Restrepo left off; the same men, the same valley, the same
commanders, but a very different look at the experience of war.
Himself, played by LaMonta Caldwell.
Himself, played by Sterling Jones.
Himself, played by Dan Kearney.
Himself, played by Juan "Doc" Restrepo.
Himself, played by Aron Hijar.
Korengal is a 2014 documentary about the War in
Afghanistan directed by Sebastian Junger.
It picks up where the film Restrepo (2010) left off, taking the viewer deeper into the experiences of the soldiers of Second
Platoon, Battle Company, 2nd Battalion, 503rd Infantry Regiment, 173rd Airborne Brigade Combat Team of the U.S.
Army while they were stationed in Korengal Valley of Kunar
Province, in eastern Afghanistan in 2007-8.
The film consists of footage of the soldiers during their
deployment, as well as interviews conducted afterward.
Most reviews of the film were favorable.
The film explores themes of us army, afghanistan war
(2001-2021), war buddies, korengal, war documentary.